# **SUZANNE PHILLIP**

LP 113 Main Road, Balmain Village, Couva, Trinidad & Tobago, WI

e-mail: phillipsuzanne2@gmail.com Cell#: 1-868-794-4714

#### **PROFILE:**

Committed to professional and personal excellence; very successful at developing strong partnerships while achieving great client satisfaction; several years experience at the Junior Management level and with company audit exercises; highly organized with strong attention to detail; sound analytical and decision making skills; Microsoft training: (Microsoft Word & Excel, familiar with Power Point and Access) strong multitasking ability and results driven.

## **EDUCATION:**

### **UWI Open Campus**

B.Sc. Management Studies (Jul 2015) Certificate Internal Auditing (Jul 2009)

## Cipriani Labour College

Certificate & Diploma Public Relations (Jul 2002) Introduction to Occupational Safety & Health (Dec 1998)

## Carapichaima/Chaguanas Senior Comprehensive

Six O'Levels

#### **Courses/Certification**

- Writing Effective Audit Reports
- AML/CFT Compliance Conference CFATF
- Microsoft Word, Excel and PowerPoint
- Effective Sales Management
- SCO UNIX System Administrator
- First Aid/CPR/AED for the workplace OSHA Services
- Credit Management 1&2
- Communication Dale Carnegie Course

#### **EXPERIENCE:**

#### British American Insurance Company (Trinidad) Limited

Audit Assistant – Internal Audit Department

May 2007 to Dec 2014

- Assisted in preparing audit programs
- Performed field work inclusive of interviews and meetings
- Researched and developed sample policies in relation to regulatory requirements
- Organized and directed all forms of communications involving matters related to audit and compliance
- Compiled supporting documentation for audit analysis and reporting

Junior Underwriter -Life Underwriting Department

Jan 2000 to Apr 2007

- Examined insurance applications for appropriate levels of coverage and process accordingly
- Obtained and managed information from field representatives, medical personnel, and other personnel
- Evaluated risk through review of relevant financial data to effectively approve insurance coverages

#### **Clico Credit Union**

Accounts Clerk/Customer Service Clerk

Apr 1990 to Apr 1997

- Accounts receivable and payable, reconciliation of bank deposits and withdrawals
- Processed Dividend Payments, Payroll Premiums, Loans, Collections & Recoveries and assisted in preparing final accounts and staff payroll
- Managed all customer requests via mail, telephone, and in-person providing exemplary service
- Planned and organized company activities, training seminars, events, scheduled meetings and administrative duties

#### REFERENCES

#### Mr. Louis Bruneau

Audit Manager (Retired) British American Insurance Company (Trinidad) Ltd. Cell#: 722-0410/361-0322

#### Mr. Andre Renie

Retired Senior Company Executive Cell#: 684-8777